<Document>
  # Lore of the Null

  To understand the Null Sector, you must understand where it rests in the galaxy.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GalacticMapMain"/>
  </Box>

  The galaxy is ruled by larger powers than the petty organizations of the Null Sector, all of whom bear little to no interest in the affairs of the lesser states. These powers hold the immense influence needed to facilitate a permanently ongoing conflict called the "Eternal War".

  The Armada is a premier galactic military super-state with a linear command structure whose self-proclaimed goal is to establish order in the galaxy at all costs, and its mission statement to spread this "Order" is through the establishment of extreme-totalitarian, dependent systems.

  Its nation consists solely of a biological robotic-minded species, an artificially created sub-species used for diplomatic engagements, and organically-reprogrammed populi abducted as tribute from “Mezzer” worlds to be used as disposable warfront soldiery.

  In other words, the Armada are [bold]everyone's[/bold] enemy, in some way or another. They are a constant threat to the Null, and all of its inhabitants.

  The Null Sector is a vast expanse infamous for being a poor and empty region of space already having been scrapped of all its worth.

  The Null Sector borders the Armada to its Galactic-East, but has no police force. It is protected by mercenary groups, private security firms and impromptu Militia.

  When Armadan Subsidiary crews threaten to approach, it is up to the militia to arise to the occasion. The Null Sector has no government, order is kept through economic incentives.

  Above all else, all Null Sector organizations fight for their own freedoms, commonly united against Armadan scout ships as lieu of a great, uncompromising threat.

  This server specifically takes place in the Lark Region of Null Sector space.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GalacticMapZoom"/>
  </Box>

  You are in the Lark Region, a small section of Null Space with no dedicated central government polity established within itself.

  Instead, authority is extended by communally-pointed ([color=#33bbff]Whitelisted[/color]) command positions in the Militia Coordinator, and Lodge Supervisor with the Sector Coordinator to oversee all regional affairs.

  All Coordinators answer to their organizations' representatives and envoys, whom answer to Rogue Sector representatives that oversee the maintenance and upkeep of the many regions in the  Null and Rogue sectors.

  Various Organizations from across the Null and the Rogue enter the Lark Region on terms of business, and for official getaway retreats. In other words, there are very few "natives" of the Lark Area itself.

</Document>
